

ISHAANABHINAV

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

STATEMENT

Hi, my name is Ishaan Abhinav, I'm a full stack web developer with over 3 years experience currently specialising in ReactNative and Django development.

I have worked with a range of languages and frameworks and I am always looking for opportunities to work with something new. The tech that I currently have the most experience working with are: ES6 Javascript, React Native & Redux, Django, Python, Java, ML, MySQL, and git.

91 - 9945257872

□ ishaanabhinav@gmail.com

Bengaluru 560021, India

PRO SKILLS

REACT NATIVE

DJANGO

HTML/CSS/JQUERY

JAVA - SPRING/STRUTS

JavaScript

PERSONAL SKILLS

Team work Communication

 $\star\star\star\star\star$ $\star\star\star\star\star$

Organisation Creative

 $\star\star\star\star\star$ $\star\star\star\star\star$

Mangement $\star\star\star\star\star$

FOLLOW ME

(2) ishaanabhinav.github.io

linkedin.com/in/ishaanabhinav/











WORK EXPERIENCE

UI ENGINEER

CBREX - Global Recruiter Exchange July 2019 - Present

I work with a small tech team and we enjoy driving the company to try new technologies. I worked on Django, React Native, Spring Boot, Struts and HTML,CSS,JQUERY along the different verticals of company product.

UI ENGINEER (Internship)

CBREX - Global Recruiter Exchange April 2018 - June 2019



PROJECTS

Hybrid Enterprise App







- Used the robust stack ReactNative+Redux+SpringBoot
- Designed complex components and higher order components.
- Integrated multiple React Native Libraries
- Implemented a complex navigation design and Redux concepts.
- · Coded and integrated spring boot api system along with specifications.

Al Engine



- Used Python + Django to implement ML algorithm.
- Integrated and used libraries such as FastText, Pandas, Numpy, scikit-learn.
- Created api's to expose the learning and result of the ML system.
- Used django libraries such as rest-framework, django-filters,bootstrap_forms,api-key.

Web Platform









- Worked on the stack HTML+CSS+Jquery with Java Struts as backend.
- Design UI views with Flexbox and media queries.
- Ensured Cross Browser Compatibility and other web design principles in the design.

EDUCATION

CMR INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY

Bachelor of Engineering - Computer Science (7.6 CGPA) 2015 - 2019

This has just been the best 4 years of my life.

Participating in almost a dozen of Hackathons, winning some of them, learning from some of them and extending my network at all of them.